Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Records WAG.022
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Subject Files
  - Subseries VII:A: Communications Department Subject Files
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "97th Congress Committee and Staff Directory", undated (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1981 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: Preliminary Report of the State Democratic Task Force of the City of New York", 1976 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Public vs. Non-Public Education in a Historical Perspective", 1982 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Public Cost of Tuition Tax Credits", 1982 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Public Funds for Public Schools of New Jersey vs. Brendan Byrne", 1978, 1981 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Statement of Dorothy Shields", 1981 (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: " Statement of Nathan Dershowitz on Behalf of the American Jewish Congress", 1982 (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Tuition Tax Credits: Their Impact on the State", 1982 (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Tuition Tax Credits: The Policy Issues and an Analysis of District of Columbia Referendum Voting Patterns", 1983 (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Wolman vs. Essex (U.S. Supreme Court), 1976 (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - Tuition Tax Credits: "Wolman vs. Walter", undated (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - United Action: Membership Letters, 1967-1978 (Box 216, Folder 21)
    - United Federation of Teachers: Strike I, 1975 (Box 216, Folder 22)
    - United Federation of Teachers: Strike II, 1975-1977 (Box 216, Folder 23)
    - United Federation of Teachers: Strike III, 1975-1977 (Box 216, Folder 24)
    - United Federation of Teachers: Strike IV, 1975-1977 (Box 216, Folder 25)
    - United Federation of Teachers: Student UFT, 1973 (Box 216, Folder 26)
    - United Teacher: Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 216, Folder 27)
    - UNESCO, 1973-1980 (Box 216, Folder 28)
    - Urban Schools Education Coalition: Membership List, undated (Box 216, Folder 29)
    - Vietnam War: Americans in Britain for U.S. Withdrawl from SE Asia, undated, 1969-1974 (Box 216, Folder 30)
    - Vietnam War: Teachers Opposed to, undated, 1971 (Box 216, Folder 31)
    - Village Voice, 1975-1977 (Box 216, Folder 32)
    - Vocational Education, 1980-1995 (Box 216, Folder 33)
    - Vouchers, 1973-1981, undated (Box 216, Folder 34)
    - Welfare Fund: Annual Reports, 1965-1967, 1971-1977 (Box 216, Folder 35)
    - Welfare Fund: Benefits, undated, 1966, 1971 (Box 216, Folder 36)
  - Subseries VII:B: President's Office Subject Files
    - Aaronson, Melvyn, 1960-1987 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Abzug, Bella, 1977 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Accountability, 1968-1970 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Accountability, 1973-1975 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Accountability: Articles, 1971-1972 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Accountability: Clippings I, 1974-1989 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Accountability: Clippings II, 1974-1989 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action, 1995 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - African-American History, 1970-1993 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - African-American Studies, 1963-1971, undated (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - African-American Studies: "A Child's Right to Learn", 1955 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - African-American Studies: Clippings, 1940-1993 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - African-American Studies: "Proportion and Rank of Afro-Americans in the NYC School System", 1966 (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - African-American Studies: Public School Expenditures in Black and White, 1942 (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - African-Americans and Education, 1988-1994 (Box 217, Folder 15)
    - African-Americans: Employment, 1957, 1990-1991 (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - African-Americans: General, 1968-1989, undated (Box 217, Folder 17)
    - African-Americans: General, 1990s (Box 217, Folder 18)
    - Agency Shop, 1961-1986 (Box 217, Folder 19)
    - Aging, 1970-1991 (Box 217, Folder 20)
    - Aging: Medicine/Medicaid, 1981-1989 (Box 217, Folder 21)
    - Aging: White House Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 217, Folder 22)
    - Agreement (UFT), 1983 (Box 217, Folder 23)
    - Agreements, 1967 (Box 217, Folder 24)
    - All-Day Neighborhood Schools (ADNS) Program, 1946, 1966-1983 (Box 217, Folder 25)
    - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Clippings, 1967-1990 (Box 217, Folder 26)
    - AFL-CIO: Conventions, 1973-1981 (Box 217, Folder 27)
    - AFL-CIO: Free Trade Union News, 1974-1975 (Box 217, Folder 28)
    - AFL-CIO: General, 1971-1972 (Box 217, Folder 29)
    - AFSCME: Clippings, 1970-1987 (Box 217, Folder 30)
    - AFSCME: Public Employees Federation (PEF), 1975-1988 (Box 217, Folder 31)
    - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1958-1992 (Box 217, Folder 32)
    - AFT: Announcements, 1961-1968, 1984-1990 (Box 217, Folder 33)
    - AFT: Anti-Shanker, General, 1977-1978, undated (Box 217, Folder 34)
    - AFT: Arts Education, Clippings, 1990-1994 (Box 217, Folder 35)
    - AFT: Bargaining, 1942-1994 (Box 217, Folder 36)
    - AFT: Bargaining, State and Local "Bulletin", 1965 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - AFT: Bargaining, State and Local "Bulletin", 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - AFT: Black Caucus, 1970-1982 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - AFT: Board, Material for Review, 1973-1975 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - AFT: Caucuses, 1960-1992, undated (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - AFT: Charles Cogen, Salute to, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - AFT: Commission on Educational Reconstruction, 1943-1944 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - AFT: Committee Reports, 1944-1963 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - AFT: Conventions, 1944-1945 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - AFT: Conventions, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - AFT: Conventions, 1963 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - AFT: Conventions, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - AFT: Conventions, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - AFT: Conventions, 1983-1984 (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - AFT: Conventions, 1988 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - AFT: Conventions, Clippings, 1964-1983 (Box 218, Folder 16)
    - AFT: Conventions, Daily Summaries, 1972-1992 (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - AFT: Conventions, Reports, 1967-1975, 1992 (Box 218, Folder 18)
    - AFT: Conventions, Roll Calls, 1967, 1969, 1972-1980 (Box 218, Folder 19)
    - AFT: Conventions, Roll Calls, 1984, 1986 (Box 218, Folder 20)
    - AFT: Correspondence, 1965-1971, 1990 (Box 218, Folder 21)
    - AFT: Executive Council, 1935-1967 (Box 218, Folder 22)
    - AFT: Executive Council, 1974 (Box 218, Folder 23)
    - AFT: Federal Aid to Students, 1960-1965 (Box 218, Folder 24)
    - AFT: Finances, 1935-1989 (Box 218, Folder 25)
    - AFT: Financial Statements, 1961-1962 (Box 218, Folder 26)
    - AFT: Financial Statements, 1962-1963 (Box 218, Folder 27)
    - AFT: Financial Statements, 1965-1966 (Box 218, Folder 28)
    - AFT: Financial Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 218, Folder 29)
    - AFT: General, undated (Box 218, Folder 30)
    - AFT: General, 1965-1993 (Box 218, Folder 31)
    - AFT: Good and Welfare, 1968, 1989 (Box 218, Folder 32)
    - AFT In Action, 1961-1974 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - AFT In the News, 1944-1973 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - AFT Locals: General, 1946-1969 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - AFT Locals: General, 1964-1989 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - AFT Locals: General, 1965, undated (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - AFT Locals: Alabama, Alaska, Arizona, Arkansas, 1958-1972 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - AFT Locals: California, General, 1945-1990 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - AFT Locals: California, Los Angeles Local 1021, 1970-1989 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - AFT Locals: California, San Francisco Local 61--Constitution, 1969-1989 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - AFT Locals: Colorado, 1963-1991 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - AFT Locals: Connecticut, 1946-1992 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - AFT Locals: Delaware, District of Columbia, Florida, 1946-1990 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - AFT Locals: Georgia, Hawaii, 1938, 1968-1979 (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - AFT Locals: Illinois, 1946-1963 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - AFT Locals: Illinois, Chicago, 1935-1990 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - AFT Locals: Indiana, 1946-1992 (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - AFT Locals: Iowa, 1946, 1992 (Box 219, Folder 17)
    - AFT Locals: Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maryland, 1946-1988 (Box 219, Folder 18)
    - AFT Locals: Massachusetts, 1944-1990 (Box 219, Folder 19)
    - AFT Locals: Michigan, 1946-1988 (Box 219, Folder 20)
    - AFT Locals: Mississippi, Missouri, 1946-1983 (Box 219, Folder 21)
    - AFT Locals: Montana, Nebraska, 1945-1957 (Box 219, Folder 22)
    - AFT Locals: New Jersey, 1946-1966 (Box 219, Folder 23)
    - AFT Locals: New Mexico, North Carolina, North Dakota, Ohio, Oregon, 1935-1990 (Box 219, Folder 24)
    - AFT Locals: Pennsylvania, 1942-1981 (Box 219, Folder 25)
    - AFT Locals: Puerto Rico, Rhode Island, South Dakota, Tennessee, Utah, Vermont, Washington, 1945-1981 (Box 219, Folder 26)
    - AFT Locals: Wisconsin, 1937-1964 (Box 219, Folder 27)
    - AFT Locals: Workers Educational Local 189, 1974-1976 (Box 219, Folder 28)
    - AFT Locals: World Federation, IFFTU, 1946-1994 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - AFT Merger, 1972-1973 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - AFT: News Clips, 1979 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - AFT: News Clips, 1980 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - AFT: News Clips, 1980-1981 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - AFT: "On Campus", 1970-1973 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - AFT: Opposition, 1974 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - AFT: Organizing, State-wide, 1970-1972 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - AFT: Origins, 1941-1945, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - AFT: Policies, 1942, 1965-1992 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - AFT: Political Action, A Teacher's Guide, 1968 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - AFT: Political Activities, 1934-1946 (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - AFT: Political Activities, 1954-1990 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - AFT: Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Convention Guides, undated (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Correspondence and Memos, 1960-1988 (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Election Committee, 1962-1979, undated (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Elections -- Candidates, 1962-1972, undated (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Elections - Cogen, 1964-1966, undated (Box 220, Folder 19)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Elections - Roth, 1962-1964, undated (Box 220, Folder 20)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Elections - Shanker, 1973-1974, undated (Box 220, Folder 21)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Membership, undated (Box 220, Folder 22)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Minutes, 1957, 1960-1968 (Box 220, Folder 23)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Minutes, 1970-1979 (Box 220, Folder 24)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Minutes, 1980-1986 (Box 220, Folder 25)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Newsletter, 1963-1983 (Box 220, Folder 26)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Notices, undated (Box 220, Folder 27)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Officers and Committee Members, 1967-1990 (Box 220, Folder 28)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Platform drafts, 1962-1973 (Box 220, Folder 29)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Platforms, 1959-1992, undated (Box 220, Folder 30)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Slates, undated (Box 220, Folder 31)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Steering Committee Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 220, Folder 32)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Steering Committee Minutes (Handwritten), 1966-1979 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - AFT: Progressive Caucus, Steering Committee Minutes, 1980-1984, 1986 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - AFT: Publications, Newsletter, 1964-1966, 1971-1973 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - AFT: Publications, "Washington Newsletter", 1965-1971 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - AFT: Quest Conference, 1985 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - AFT: Quest Conference, Resource Papers, 1981 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - AFT: Quest Consortium Yearbook, 1972 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - AFT: Women's Rights, Policy Resolutions, 1970 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - AFT: Workshops, 1946-1969 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - Anti-Semitism, 1965-1986 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - A. Philip Randolph Institute: Publications, 1969, 1971, undated (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Art Education, 1970s (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Art Education: Awards, 1979-1991 (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - Art Education: Clippings, 1970-1990 (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - Art Education: UFT Art Committee, 1940, 1964-1966, 1974-1990 (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - Asian-American Students, 1979-1992 (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - Assault/Robbery Reports: Boys and Girls High School, 1975-1978 (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - Athletics: Coaches, 1945, 1965-1987 (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - Athletics: Co-ed, 1970-1990 (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - Athletics: College Recruitment, 1988-1990 (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - Athletics: Fields, 1975, 1980-1990 (Box 221, Folder 21)
    - Athletics: Finance, 1970-1990 (Box 221, Folder 22)
    - Athletics: Safety, 1980-1990 (Box 221, Folder 23)
    - Attendance: Drop-out Problem, 1964, 1970-1972 (Box 221, Folder 24)
    - Attendance: Drop-out Problem, Clippings, 1980-1990 (Box 221, Folder 25)
    - Attendance: Non-NYC, 1964-1971, 1983-1990 (Box 221, Folder 26)
    - Attendance: Problems, 1970-1980 (Box 221, Folder 27)
    - Attendance: Problems, Clippings, 1970-1980s (Box 221, Folder 28)
    - Attendance: Solutions, 1968-1990 (Box 221, Folder 29)
    - Attendance: Statistics, 1972-1989 (Box 221, Folder 30)
    - Attendance Teachers, 1940s, 1960-1990 (Box 221, Folder 31)
    - Back to Basics: Grading and Testing, 1979-1980, 1993 (Box 221, Folder 32)
    - Back to Basics: "Minimum Requirements for Schools in New York State", 1978 (Box 221, Folder 33)
    - Back to Basics: "Regents Seek Public Reactions to New Competency Standards", undated (Box 221, Folder 34)
    - Back to Basics: Testing, 1974, 1993, undated (Box 221, Folder 35)
    - Back to Basics: Testing, articles, 1981-1988 (Box 221, Folder 36)
    - Beagle, Simon, 1986, 1979, undated (Box 221, Folder 37)
    - Beame, Abraham: Clippings and Press Releases, 1974-1980 (Box 221, Folder 38)
    - Bilingual Education, 1992-1994 (Box 221, Folder 39)
    - Bilingual Education: Articles, " The Relative Proficiency of Limited Proficient Students:, 1980 (Box 221, Folder 40)
    - Bilingual Education: Articles and Pamphlets, 1980 (Box 221, Folder 41)
    - Bilingual Education: Board of education, 1968-1979 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Bilingual Education: Bibliographic Studies, 1974, 1975, undated (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Bilingual Education: Clippings, 1967-1992 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Bilingual Education: English as Official Language, 1986-1987, undated (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Bilingual Education: Federal Legislation, 1969-1984 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Bilingual Education: "Language, Ethnicity, and the Schools", 1977 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Bilingual Education: Legal Decisions, 1973-1991 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Bilingual Education: New York State Policy, 1970-1980 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Bilingual Education: UFT,AFT, NYSUT, 1967-1989 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Bilingual Education: Biographical, 1937-1967, undated (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Black Heritage Committee, 1979-1993 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Black-Jewish Relations, 1964-1985 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Board of Education, 1971-1995 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - Board of Education: Attacks on, 1966-1981 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Board of Education: Attacks on, 1984-1994 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Board of Education: Baker, Gwendolyn, 1986-1991 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Board of Education: Betanzos, Amalia, 1987 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Board of Education: Buildings, After School use of, 1971-1994 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - Board of Education: Buildings, Problems (Clippings), 1965-1994 (Box 222, Folder 19)
    - Board of Education: Buildings, Repairs, 1965-1994 (Box 222, Folder 20)
    - Board of Education: By-laws, 1964 (Box 222, Folder 21)
    - Board of Education: By-laws, 1967-1968, 1977 (Box 222, Folder 22)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor, Clippings, 1983-1988 (Box 222, Folder 23)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor Alvarado, 1982-1984 (Box 222, Folder 24)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor Anker, Irving, 1970-1978 (Box 222, Folder 25)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor Contines, 1993-1994 (Box 222, Folder 26)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor Fernandez, 1989-1993 (Box 222, Folder 27)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor Macchiarola, 1978-1983 (Box 222, Folder 28)
    - Board of Education: Chancellor Quinones, 1984-1987 (Box 222, Folder 29)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1962-1964 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1966-1967 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1969 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1970-1971 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1972 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jan 1973-Jun 1973 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jul 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jan 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jul 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1975-1977 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, 1978 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jan 1979-Jun 1979 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jul 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jan 1980-Jun 1980 (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jul 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jan 1981-Jun 1981 (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jul 1981-Dec 1981 (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jan 1982-Jun 1982 (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - Board of Education: Circulars, Jul 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Board of Education: Clippings, 1970-1973 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Board of Education: Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Board of Education: Clippings, 1990-1994 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Board of Education: Cummings, Mary A., 1975, 1991-1994 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Board of Education: Demolition of Underutilized Buildings, 1972-1994 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Board of Education: Deputy Chancellors, 1970-1988 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Board of Education: Headquarters Staff, 1970-1990 (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Board of Education: Members, Clippings, 1969-1994 (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - Board of Education: Monserrat, Joseph, 1974-1975 (Box 224, Folder 9)
    - Board of Education: Naming Schools, Clippings, 1971-1994 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - Board of Education: Policy of Excellence, 1965, undated (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Board of Education: Publication, High Points, 1965-1971 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - Board of Education: Publication, Staff Bulletin, 1962-1972 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - Board of Education: Publication, Strengthening Democracy, 1951-1960 (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - Board of Education: Publications, misc., 1980-1987 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - Board of Education: Pupil Enrollment Figures, 1965-1994 (Box 224, Folder 16)
    - Board of Education: Race Issues, 1977-1990 (Box 224, Folder 17)
    - Board of Education: Regan, Jim, 1973-1986 (Box 224, Folder 18)
    - Board of Education: Reorganization Complaints, 1942-1976 (Box 224, Folder 19)
    - Board of Education: Reorganization Complaints, 1977-1994 (Box 224, Folder 20)
    - Board of Education: Robinson, Isaiah, 1971-1984 (Box 224, Folder 21)
    - Board of Education: School Calendar, 1965-1993 (Box 224, Folder 22)
    - Board of Education: School Construction, Clippings, 1969-1994 (Box 224, Folder 23)
    - Board of Education: Superintendents, 1962-1988 (Box 224, Folder 24)
    - Board of Education: Teachers, Supply of, 1963-1994 (Box 224, Folder 25)
    - Board of Education: Transportation, 1945, 1977-1991 (Box 224, Folder 26)
    - Board of Education: Wagner, Robert III, 1983-1990 (Box 224, Folder 27)
    - Board of Examiners: Attacks on I, 1962-1988 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Board of Examiners: Attacks on II, 1967-1988 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Board of Examiners: Attacks on, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Boston University: Chelsea Schools, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Budget: NYC, 1985-1990 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Budget: NYC, 1991-1994 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Child Guidance, 1974 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Business/Private Sector and Education, 1972-1989 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Business/Private Sector and Education: Corporate, 1980s-1990s (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Business/Private Sector and Education: Philanthropy, 1982-1990 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Busing: Articles and Bibliographies, 1972-1983 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Busing: Clippings, 1972-1979 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Busing: Government Perspective, 1972-1985 (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - Busing: Legal Decisions, 1977-1991 (Box 225, Folder 14)
    - Busing: National, 1974-1991 (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - Busing: New York City, 1964-1993 (Box 225, Folder 16)
    - Carey, Hugh L., 1970-1978 (Box 225, Folder 17)
    - Cartoons, 1960s-1990s (Box 225, Folder 18)
    - Catholic Schools: Clippings, 1970s-1993 (Box 225, Folder 19)
    - Catholic Schools: Strikes, 1970s (Box 225, Folder 20)
    - Catholic Schools: Strikes, 1980s-1994 (Box 225, Folder 21)
    - Catholic Schools: Unions, 1955, 1975-1982 (Box 225, Folder 22)
    - Caucuses (AFT): Progressive, 1982 (Box 225, Folder 23)
    - Caucuses (AFT): United Action, 1986 (Box 225, Folder 24)
    - Caucuses (NYSUT): Grassroots, 1974 (Box 225, Folder 25)
    - Caucuses (NYSUT): Teacher Democracy, 1974-1976 (Box 225, Folder 26)
    - Caucuses (UFT): Chalk Dust, 1988 (Box 225, Folder 27)
    - Caucuses (UFT): General, 1977 (Box 225, Folder 28)
    - Caucuses (UFT): Rank and File, 1960-1975 (Box 225, Folder 29)
    - Caucuses (UFT): Teachers Action (TAX), 1969-1980 (Box 225, Folder 30)
    - Caucuses (UFT): Unity, 1971-1988 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Center for Urban Education, 1966 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements, 1961-1965 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, 1966-1975 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, Jan 1976-Feb 1976 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, Mar 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, May 1976-Jul 1976 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, Aug 1976-Sep 1976 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, Oct 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, 1977-1980 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Announcements and Notices, undated (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Chapter Chairmen: CUNY, undated (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Grievances, How to File, undated (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Handbook, second edition, 1970 (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Political Action, Endorsements, 1976 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Political Action, Misc., 1975-1976 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Tenure Training Panel, undated (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Training Course, 1976, undated (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - Chapter Chairmen: Training Manuel, 1976 (Box 226, Folder 19)
    - Charter Revision: New York State, 1970-1982 (Box 226, Folder 20)
    - Charter Revision: New York State, Clippings, 1967-1990 (Box 226, Folder 21)
    - Chess, 1985-1994 (Box 226, Folder 22)
    - Child Abuse, 1970-1994 (Box 226, Folder 23)
    - Child Labor, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 24)
    - Children, 1970-1995 (Box 226, Folder 25)
    - Children: Foster Homes, 1974-1994 (Box 226, Folder 26)
    - Children: Health, 1971-1990 (Box 226, Folder 27)